{
    "subject": "resource/Skog",
    "predicate": "property/members",
    "object": "\u00d8ystein Gj\u00e6rder Bruvik",
    "human_readable": "Skog's members include \u00d8ystein Gj\u00e6rder Bruvik.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9257479906082153,
            "question": "What is the name of the organization that \u00d8ystein Gj\u00e6rder Bruvik is a member of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9093005061149597,
            "question": "Who is \u00d8ystein Gj\u00e6rder Bruvik?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.89372718334198,
            "question": "What group does \u00d8ystein Gj\u00e6rder Bruvik belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8537814617156982,
            "question": "Who are some members of Skog's?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8246291875839233,
            "question": "Is \u00d8ystein Gj\u00e6rder Bruvik part of an organization?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7538198828697205,
            "question": "Can you name a member of Skog's?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7502702474594116,
            "question": "What is the full name of a member of Skog's?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6933789253234863,
            "question": "What kind of group is Skog's?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5830466747283936,
            "question": "Does Skog's have any famous members?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46038132905960083,
            "question": "Is there more than one person in Skog's?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Skog's members include \u00d8ystein Gj\u00e6rder Bruvik.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5647_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Skog's have any famous members?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5647_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of group is Skog's?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5647_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the full name of a member of Skog's?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5647_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5647_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5647_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5647_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5647_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5647_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5647_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5647_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5647_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5647_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5647_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that according to the context information, Skog was a rock band from Bergen, Norway, which formed in the early 1990s and split up at the end of the same decade. The group consisted of Anders Waage Nilsen, \u00d8ystein Gj\u00e6rder Bruvik, Eirik Glambek B\u00f8e and Erlend \u00d8ye. This directly supports the statement that Skog's members include \u00d8ystein Gj\u00e6rder Bruvik."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the band Skog and its members, including \u00d8ystein Gj\u00e6rder Bruvik. Therefore, the statement \"Skog's members include \u00d8ystein Gj\u00e6rder Bruvik\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}